(Leonard:)This is weird, right?
(Sheldon:)Pop-Pop was the only one in my family
who encouraged me to pursue science.
(Sheldon:)But you didn't bring him back, did you?
(Sheldon:)No. Instead, I got Lincoln Logs.
Now, you can build a lot of neat things
out of Lincoln Logs...
...but Pop-Pop ain't one of them.
(Sheldon:)And now you're here asking me
for something. To save you.
(Sheldon:)Well, sorry, Mr. Kringle.
But today's not your day.
(Sheldon:)I'm leaving you here to rot
and I hope the ogres feast on your bones.
(Sheldon:)I take the skeleton key,
toss it into the chasm...
...and on the way out give Santa a swift kick
in his bowl full ofjelly.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Leonard:)So Wolowitz and Stuart are paralyzed,
Santa's dead...
(Leonard:)...and I picked this over having sex
with my girlfriend.